<IFileIO>
	<Class name="IFileIO">
		<summary>
			Interface defining a contract for basic file operations.
		</summary>
	</Class>

	<Properties>
		<!-- No properties defined for this interface. -->
	</Properties>

	<Methods>
		<Instance name="Exists[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Checks if the specified file exists at the given file path.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to check for existence.</param>
			<returns>True if the file exists; otherwise, false.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="OpenRead[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Opens the specified file for reading.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to open for reading.</param>
			<returns>A stream for reading the contents of the file.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="OpenWrite[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Opens the specified file for writing, creating the file if it does not exist.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to open for writing.</param>
			<returns>A stream for writing to the file.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="Rename[EntryPath,EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Renames the file specified by the source file path to the destination file path.
			</summary>
			<param name="sourceFilePath">The current path of the file to be renamed.</param>
			<param name="destinationFilePath">The new path to which the file should be renamed.</param>
			<returns>True if the renaming was successful; otherwise, false.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="Delete[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Deletes the file at the specified file path.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to delete.</param>
			<returns>True if the file was successfully deleted; otherwise, false.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="GetFileTimestamps[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Gets the creation, last access, and last write timestamps of the specified file.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to get timestamps for.</param>
			<returns>
				A <see cref="FileTimestamps"/> object containing the timestamps.
			</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="SetFileTimestamps[EntryPath,FileTimestamps]">
			<summary>
				Sets the creation, last access, and last write timestamps of the specified file.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to set timestamps for.</param>
			<param name="timestamps">A <see cref="FileTimestamps"/> object containing the timestamps to set.</param>
			<returns>True if the timestamps were successfully set; otherwise, false.</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="GetFileAttributes[EntryPath]">
			<summary>
				Gets the attributes of the specified file.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to get attributes for.</param>
			<returns>
				A <see cref="FileAttributes"/> object representing the attributes of the file.
			</returns>
		</Instance>

		<Instance name="SetFileAttributes[EntryPath,FileAttributes]">
			<summary>
				Sets the attributes of the specified file.
			</summary>
			<param name="path">The path of the file to set attributes for.</param>
			<param name="attributes">A <see cref="FileAttributes"/> object representing the attributes to set.</param>
			<returns>True if the attributes were successfully set; otherwise, false.</returns>
		</Instance>
	</Methods>
</IFileIO>
